bigfix.com 2006-10-24

# BIGFIX, INC. - SECURITY CONFIGURATION MANAGEMENT - VULNERABILITY MANAGEMENT - ENDPOINT SECURITY - PATCH MANAGEMENT

BigFix Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy Matters to Us**

BigFix respects your privacy and is committed to protecting all personal information you choose to share with us. This privacy statement explains when we might ask you for personal information, what we might do with it, and how we will protect its confidentiality. It also explains what information we might automatically collect when you access our Web site or that we might otherwise receive about you. This privacy statement does not cover the practices of third party businesses that we do not control or individuals that we do not employ or manage. 

**When Do We Ask for Your Personal Information**

Where possible, we enable you to browse our Web site without providing us with any personally identifiable information. When we do ask you for personally identifiable information, we only use it for specific purposes described in this privacy statement and in order to enhance the service we provide to you. 

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. Examples include: receiving information about BigFix products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, filling out a survey, downloading software or license keys, requesting additional information, applying to our Partner Program, logging into certain limited-access sections of our Web site (such as for support, partners, press), and signing up for an event or training. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, information about your job function, and information about your company. 

Access to certain limited-access portions of our Web site may require a login id and a password. The use of such web pages, and the information or programs downloadable from them, may be governed by a written agreement between your employer and BigFix. Your personal information may be retained by BigFix to verify compliance with the agreement, log software licenses granted, to track software downloaded from those pages, or track usage of other applications available on those pages. 

**Other Ways We May Collect Information**

Our Web site may automatically collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the site; the pages that you access while at the site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site. You can find more details about automatically collected information in the section below called “Use of Cookies and Tracking Information.” 

From time to time, BigFix may receive personal information from third party business partners and vendors. We only use such information if we believe that it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws. 

**How Do We Use Your Personal Information**

Personal information collected by this Web site will be used to operate the Web site and to provide service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) that you have requested or authorized. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside of BigFix with your consent, or as described in this privacy statement. 

We may use your personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Web site and any related BigFix products or services, and to make our Web site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Web site to your particular preference or interests. We may merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. 

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the products or services that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other BigFix products and services. 

When you sign up for a newsletter or agree to receive promotional e-mail, we may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. Each e-mail communication includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication. 

**When We May Share Your Personal Information**

_With Your Consent._ For example, with your permission, we may share information with BigFix partners so they may send you information about their products and services. 

_Partners and Agents._ We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

_Compliance With Law; Protection of BigFix and Others._ BigFix may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BigFix; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BigFix; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of BigFix employees or agents, users of BigFix products or services, or members of the public. 

_Transfer of Assets._ BigFix is an independent company. However, personal information provided to BigFix may be transferred in the event that all or substantially all of the assets of the company are acquired by a third party whether by merger, acquisition, reorganization or otherwise, or in the unlikely event that BigFix goes out of business or enters bankruptcy. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any transferee may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this privacy statement. 

**Control of your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise described in this statement, we will not share personal information you provide to us without your permission. In addition, as described below, you may contact us at any time to update or delete your personal information. 

On occasion, we may send you email informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services that may be offered by BigFix, contacting you is an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service(s) you have elected to receive. 

Personal information collected on our Web site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which BigFix or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Keeping Your Personal Information Secure**

We use a variety of physical, digital and managerial technologies and procedures to help protect your client information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. While we strive to protect your client information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your confidential data when you are on the Internet. 

**Protection of Children's Personal Information**

This Web site is intended for general audiences and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 

**Use of Cookies and Tracking Information**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your hard disk when you browse a Web site. When you visit our Web site, BigFix may store a cookie on your computer's hard drive. This allows us to enhance your ability to use our Web site by recognizing you when you visit or to optimize the information or features presented to you based on your demonstrated areas of interest. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of our site that are visited most frequently. This aggregate traffic information can be used to enhance the content of our site and make your experience more enjoyable. You are always welcome to visit our Web site with cookies disabled. However, you made be asked to re-enter information that you have provided before (such as your name or contact information). In addition, certain capabilities of our Web site, such as use of limited-access portions, personalization or special interactivity features, may not function fully without cookies. If you have requested information or services from us or have opted in to third-party mailing lists, you may receive email from us that references content that contains a unique identifier. Such content sometimes takes the form of tiny, transparent images that are sometimes called "clear GIFs" or an equivalent. These clear GIFs may be used to assist in delivering a cookie from our Web site. These cookies may be used to compile aggregated statistics about usage of our Web site, such as how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on one of our Web pages, a blog or a newsletter. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies. In addition, such clear GIFs may sometimes be used to deliver co-branded services. We may also include clear GIFs in promotional email messages, newsletters, and other communications in order to determine whether messages have been opened or acted upon. In some instances, clear GIFs may be placed by third-party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These clear GIFs may be used by such service providers to store a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. 

**Third Party Web Sites**

Our Web site contains links to other sites, such as those of our business partners, articles or sources of information that we believe visitors to our site may find interesting. BigFix does not share your personal information with those Web sites based on the link and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

**Notification of Changes**

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the date at the top of this privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our Web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

**We Welcome Your Comments**

You may contact us at any time with any privacy questions or concerns that you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. 

If you ever have questions or concerns about the personal information you have provided us, please email us at [bigfix-privacy at bigfix.com](mailto:bigfix-privacy@bigfix.com) or via postal mail at: ****

**BigFix, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
6121 Hollis St.  
Emeryville, CA 94608  
**

BigFix welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that we have not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
